(Bernadette:)What are you looking at?
(Howard:)Pictures of my dad and me
when I was a kid.
- That's nice.
- I gotta tell you...
(Howard:)...as angry as I am at Sheldon for blabbing...
...he did a hell of ajob
organizing this closet.
(Howard:)Look at this.
"Photos of Wolowitz Family
Before Father Left Forever."
Look. Check out 9-year-old Howie
with cornrows.
(Howard:)Neither race was happy
to see me with those.
Think you can take a break?
- Why?
- Got a little surprise for you.
(Howard:)Come on.
(Howard:)Oh, honey...
(Howard:)...I am in no mood to have sex tonight.
I mean, I'll lay there
if you absolutely have to have it, but...
(Penny:)Oh.
(Howard:)What are you guys doing here?
You weren't sure whether you wanted
to know what was in your dad's letter...